

# David Laurenzi Design

(818) 324 5056 davidlaurenzi@gmail.com behance.net/davidlaurenzi davidlaurenzi.myportfolio.com

#### Skills & Tools

#### Skills

User Research
Competitive Analysis
User Flow Diagramming
Wireframing
Prototyping
Preference Testing
Project Management
Art Direction

Brand Ideation

UX/UI Design

Graphic Design

Illustration

Print Production

Hi-Res Builds

Color Editing

Mechanicals

#### Tools

Sketch

Figma

Photoshop

Illustrator

InDesign

Bridge

Acrobat

Flinto

InVision

# Education

## CareerFoundry

UI Design Program 2020-2021

## DesignLab

UX Academy Foundation 2020

# University of the Arts

Philadelphia, PA BFA in Illustration, 1992

### **Profile**

UX/UI Designer with a background of award-winning graphic design. More than two decades of experience in point-of-purchase display and packaging. Developed temporary, permanent, and semi-permanent display vehicles, brand and corporate identities, and sales collateral for clients in entertainment, retail, pharmaceutical and cosmetic industries. Recognized by P.O.P. Times, POPAI, PROMAXGAMES, and Clio Awards. Selected as Juror for 2019 Clio Entertainment Awards.

#### Career

David Laurenzi Design Marina del Rey, CA

Dec. 2019-Present

- · Freelance graphic design creating concept art for P.O.P.
- · Production art for multi-lingual packaging.
- · Branding and logo design.

## Q Design Industries El Segundo, CA

2009-2019

Creative director and designer, responsible for concept, design and final pre-press production of temporary corrugate P.O.P. displays incorporating specialty materials, flexographic, and litho printing. Production of display renderings, half and full scale mock-ups as well as original art, package design, and collateral materials. Worked directly with clients to interpret and fulfill their needs on time and beyond expectation.

- $\cdot$  Lead designer for large-scale campaigns such as: Harry Potter 7A & B, Fantastic Beasts, Batman v Superman, Transformers, etc.
- · Client list including: Abus, Activision, Cyanotech, Irwin Naturals, Maglite, Ole Smoky, Paramount, Quicksilver, Skullcandy, Sony, Square Enix, Warner, Bros., Western Digital, WGN.

# Origin LLC. Burbank, CA

1998-2009

Senior Graphic Designer producing P.O.P. displays as well as package, and collateral material design and original key art. Responsible for the design and concept of entire display campaigns in retail channels such as Best Buy, Target, Walmart, Costco, Sam's Club, et. al.

- · Lead designer on The Grinch, and Monsters Inc., two of the largest entertainment campaigns at the time, worth \$2.5 and \$1.5 million respectively.
- · Client list including: Disney, DreamWorks, Focus Features, Fox, Lion's Gate, Microsoft, New Line, Nickelodeon, Nintendo, Paramount, Sony Pictures, Universal Pictures.